Contact

quijuana.goodman@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/quijuanagoodman (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Nursing Hospitals

Certifications

Lean Six Sigma Green Belt Certification Interqual Certified Instructor Accredited Case Manager Lean Six Sigma Champion

Honors-Awards

The Glowing Lamp for the Nurse Award

Key Contributor

Quijuana Goodman

Division Vice President Care Coordination at Kindred Healthcare Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Healthcare Executive leader professional with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Creator of career and lifestyle blog The Working Mom Chronicles, a community for career minded moms, balancing a successful career with home.

Experience

Kindred Healthcare
3 years 4 months

Division Vice President
March 2020 - Present (5 months)
Houston, Texas, United States

District Director Case Management April 2017 - March 2020 (3 years) Houston, Texas

The Working Mom Chronicles
Content Creator
October 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Experienced Healthcare Executive leader professional with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Created of career and lifestyle blog The Working Mom Chronicles, a community for career minded mom's balancing a successful career with home.

Sentara Healthcare
8 years 6 months

System Director Integrated Care Management
2015 - April 2017 (2 years)

Manager Care Coordination
April 2012 - September 2015 (3 years 6 months)

Team Coordinator/Supervisor Care Coordination September 2010 - April 2012 (1 year 8 months)

Clinical Care Coordinator November 2008 - September 2010 (1 year 11 months)

Amerigroup Lead Nurse Case Manager April 2007 - October 2008 (1 year 7 months) Virginia Beach, Virginia

Bon Secours Health System

Nurse Case Manager

October 2006 - October 2008 (2 years 1 month)

US Navy Nurse Corp Officer August 2002 - September 2006 (4 years 2 months)

Education

Loyola University New Orleans

MSN, Health/Health Care Administration/Management · (2010 - 2012)

University of Holy Cross
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1997 - 2002)